Guide to the Luis Leal Papers, 1946-1985
Department of Special Collections
- Series 6: Reference Materials
  - Subseries E: Luis Leal research folder files on additional latin american authors. A-Z
    - Rabassa, Gregory. Rama, Angel. Reyes, Salvador. Reyles, Carlos. Ricci, Julio. Rodríguez, Fueile. Rodríguez, Luis Felipe. Rodríguez-Alcala, Hugo. Rodríguez Émbul, Luis. Rodríguez Mendoza, Emilio. Rodríguez Tomen, Humberto. Rojas, Manuel. Rojas, Ricardo. Romero, Francisco. Rowe, William. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Saens, Jaime. Salazar Bondy, Sebastián. Salormé. Samayoa Chinchilla, Carlos. Salazar Arué, Salvador. Sánchez, Luis Alberto. Sánchez, Luis Rafael. Sánchez-Reulet, Anibal. Sanín Cano, Baldomero. Santa Cruz, Rosendo. Santiván, Fernando. Sardiña, Ricardo R. Sarduy, Severo. Selva, Salomón de la. Silva, Medardo Angel. Silva Valdes, Fernan. Sosa, Roberto. Soto, Pedro Juan. Storni, Alfonsin. Suárez, Gastón. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Tabaré J. Freire, Javier de Viena. Tejada, Luis de. Téllez, Hernando. Trejo, Oswaldo. Triana, José. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Ugarte, Manuel. Urbaneja Alchelpohl, Manuel. Uribe Piedrahita, César. (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Valdelomar, Abraham. Valle, Gerardo del. Valle, Rafael Heliodoro. Valdés, Igor Iván. Valenzuela, Luisa. Vargas Vila, J.M. Vega, Garcilaso de la. Velarde, Héctor. Vera, Gonzalo. Vera, Pedro Jorge. Vergara y Vergara, José María. Villaverde, Cirilio. Villor B., Aurora. Vitier, Medardo. (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Wernicke, Enrique. Wilde, Eduardo. (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Zarate Moreno, Jesús. Zell, Rosa Hilda. Zorrilla de San Martín, Juan (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Subseries F: Luis Leal research folder files on miscellaneous latin american literature & culture in general
    - Latin american literature & culture in general. (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Subseries G: Luis Leal research folder files on general topics. (not latin america or Mexico). A-Z
    - American literature. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Art. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Cervantes, Miguel de. (cont...) (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Cervantes, Miguel de. (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Cervantes, Miguel de. (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Cervantes - Persiles. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Cervantes - Teatro. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Comparative literature. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Dostoevsky. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Faulkener, William. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Hebreo, León. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Kafka, Franz. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Language. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Literary criticism. (cont...) (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Literary criticism. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Literary criticism. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - MLA (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - MLA - Commission on minority groups. (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - National endowment fo humanities. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - New York State Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Spain & Portugal. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Ortega Y Gasset. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Pirandello. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Quevedo. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Portugal. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Rojas, Fernando de. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Romanticismo. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Spain - Siglo de oro. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Spain - 18th & 19th Centuries. (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Spain - Siglo XX. (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Spain - País. (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Unamuno. (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - University of Illinois. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - University of San Francisco. (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous research folder files
    - Notes on Mexico. (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Subseries I: Words in the english language, taken from the spanish language
    - Words in the english language taken from the spanish language. (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Subseries J: Research card files, by Luis Leal
    - Abbreviations for the following bibliographies: Abreviaturas: A-Z Teoría literaria I. Estudios Literatura indigena A. Generales B. Períodos y movimientos 1. Prehispano 2. Novohispano 3. Ncional 4. Modernismo 5. Postmodernismo 6. Revolución 7. Vanguardia 8. Contemporaneo (cont...) (Box 104)
    - Abbreviations for the following bibliographies. I. Estudios Literatura indigena C. Genero literario 1. Poesia 2. Novela 2. General Bibliographies: 3. Crítica: Cuento y leyenda 4. Crítica: Teatro 5. Crítica: Ensayo y crítica II. Antologías y colecciones A. Coleccion de textos B. Antologias 1. Generales 2. Poesia 3. Narrativa 4. Teatro 5. Ensayos y otras prosas (cont...) (Box 105)
    - General bibliographies III. Biografía A. Biografias B. Seudonimos 1. Estudios y listas 2. No recogidos IV. Bibliografías A. Generales B. Poesía C. Narrativa D. Teatro V. Revistas y períodismo A. Indices crítica y estudios 3. Titles, etc.; Theses about Mexico: B. Titutlos VI. Literatura mexicana: Tesis doctorales A. Estudios B. Sobre temas C. Sobre autores VII. Lengua A. Estudios B. Diccionario, glosario, etc. VIII. Obras generales (en las que se habla de la literatura mexicana) A. Estudios B. Antologías (Box 106)
    - Bibliography of the legend: Leyenda. La leyenda autores A-Z. Anonima. Miscellaneous bibliographies: Historica (cronologica) Novela Temas (cont...) (Box 107)
    - Miscellaneous bibliography: Volador: notes Dario de México Crítica Residuos (Box 108)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Abad - Aznar. (Box 109)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Azuela - Calvillo. (Box 110)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Calleja - Custodio. (Box 111)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Chabat - Figueroa, Fr. Francisco. (Box 112)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Figueroa - González, Guerrero. (Box 113)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. González Gutiérrez, Juanes - Izquierdo Albiñana, A. (Box 114)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. J. R. G. - López y Fuentes, Gregorio. (Box 115)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Loreley-Garza, María Luisa - Mora, José María Luis. (Box 116)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Mora, José María Luis - Olaguíbel, Francisco M. de. (Box 117)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Olaguíbel, Francisco M. de - Pellicer, Carlos. (Box 118)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Penagos, Ranulfo - Reyes Alfonso. (Box 119)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Reyes Alfonso - Romero, José Rubén. (Box 120)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Romero, José Rubén - Salazar Mallén, Rubén. (Box 121)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Saldaña, Jorge Isaac - Torri Máyenz, Julio. (Box 122)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Torri Máyenz, Julio - Villaurrutia, Xavier. (Box 123)
    - Bibliography: Mexican authors. Villaurrutia, Xavier - Zorrilla. Also, obras publicadas con seudónimo, and Autores extranjeros en México. (Box 124)
    - "Historia de la literatura mexicana" - for the unpublished manuscript ,by Luis Leal. I. General bibliography & 16th century authors (Box 125)
    - "Historia de la literatura mexicana" - for the unpublished manuscript, by Luis Leal II. 17th - 18th - 19th - 20th century authors (Box 126)
    - "Historia de la literatura mexicana" - for the unpublished manuscript, by Luis Leal III. Index of authors & index of title. Also, various notes: English-Spanish computer dictionary (unpublished) (Box 127)
    - Research notes on Mexico. Authors: A-L (Box 128)
    - Research notes on Mexico. Authors: M-S (Box 129)
    - Research notes on Mexico. Authors: T-Z Mexican fiction writers: A-J (Box 130)
    - Mexican fiction writers: L-S (Box 131)
    - Mexican fiction writers: T-Z General reserch notes: A-C (Box 132)
    - General reserch notes: Ch-R (Box 133)
    - General reserch notes: S-Z Azuela. (Box 134)
  - Subseries K: Research notes by Luis Leal
    - I. Cuento mexicano: A-L Original and supplementary notes for book Bibliografía del cuento mexicano (1958) by Luis Leal (Box 135)
    - II. Cuento mexicano: M-Z Original and supplementary notes for book Bibliografía del cuento mexicano (1958) by Luis Leal (Box 136)
    - Cuento hispanoamericano - Original supplementary notes for the book Historia del cuento hispanoamericano (1971) by Luis Leal (Box 137)
    - Bibliography of central american literature. Unpublished (Box 138)
    - Bibliography of theses and dissertations about latin american literature (Box 139)
    - Bibliography on hispanoamérica (crítica, crítica y teoría, miscellaneous) (Box 140)
    - Bibliography for book Breve historia de la iteratura hispanoamericana (1971) by Luis Leal. (I. incluido) (Box 141)
    - Bibliography for book Breve historia de la iteratura hispanoamericana (1971) by Luis Leal. (II. no incluido) (Box 142)
    - Miscellaneous notes on theory of the novel, theory of the short story, and términos retoricos (Box 143)
    - Literature hispanoamericana. Authors: A - González (Box 144)
    - Literature hispanoamericana. Authors: Güiraldes - M (Box 145)
    - Literature hispanoamericana. Authors: N - S (Box 146)
    - Literature hispanoamericana. Authors: T - Z (Box 147)
  - Subseries L: Research notes on Sor Juana by Luis Leal
    - Research notes on Sor Juana (Box 148)
  - Subseries M: Luis Leal research notes on novel Jicotencal, written after Luis Leal article was published. (notes unpublished) Also, Notes for book: Leyenda mexicana
    - Luis Leal research notes on novel Jicotencal, written after Luis Leal article was published. (notes unpublished) Also, notes for book: Leyenda mexicana (Box 149)
  - Subseries N: Student papers on latin american literature and culture. A-Q
    - Aguiler Chávez, Manuel (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Aguilera Malta, Demetrio (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Amorim, Enrique (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Anderson Imbert, Enrique (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Arciniegas, Germán (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Arévalo Martínez, Rafael (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Arguedas, Alcides (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Arguedas, José María (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Asturias, Miguel Angel (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Barrios, Eduardo (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Bioy Casares, Adolfo (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Bleste Gana, Alberto (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Bombal, María Luisa (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Bosch, Juan (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Brunet, Marta (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Caballero Calderón, Eduardo (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Cardoza y Aragón, Luis (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Carpentier, Alejo (cont...) (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Carpentier, Alejo (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Casal, Julian del (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Cuadra, José de la (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Darío, Rubén (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Denevi, Marco (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - D'tlalmar, Augusto (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Díaz, Alfaro (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Díaz Rodríguez, Manuel (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Díaz Sánchez, Ramón (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Dobles, Fabían (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Donoso, José (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Droguett, Carlos (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Gallegos, Rómulo (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Gálvez, Manuel (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - García, Márquez (cont...) (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - García, Márquez (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Guatemala (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Gutiérrez, Joaquín (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Hernández, Juan José (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Herrera, Flavio (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Icaza, Jorge (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Irisarri (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Isaacs, Jorge (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Korsi, Demetrio (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Laguerre, Enrique A. (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Larreta (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Lillo, Baldomero (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Lindo, Hugo (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - López Albújar, Enrique (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - López Gómez, Adel (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Loveira, Carlos (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Lynch, Benito (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Mallea, Eduardo (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Mañach, Jorge (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Mariátegui, Carlos (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Marinello, Juan (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Mármol, José (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Márquez Salas, Antonio (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Marti, José (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Mera, Juan León (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Monteforte Toledo, Mario (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Novas Calvo, Lindo (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Onetti, Juan Carlos (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Ortiz, Fernando (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Palma, Ricardo (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Payró, Roberto J. (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Picón-Salas, Mariano (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Prieto, Jenaro (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Puig, Manuel (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Quiroga, Horacio (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Subseries O: Student papers on latin american literature and culture and various topics. R-Z
    - Reyles, Carlos (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Rivera, José Eustasio (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Roa Bastos, A. (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Rodó, José Enrique (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Rojas, Manuel (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Sábato, Ernesto (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Salazar Bondy, Sebastían (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Sánchez, Florencio (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Sánchez, Luis Alberto (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Silva, José Asunción (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Solarte, Tristan (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Ugarte, Manuel (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - UribePiedrahita, César (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Uslar Pietri, Arturo (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Vargas Llosa, Mario (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Viviana, Javier de (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Bibliographies (cont...) (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Bibliographies (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Cuento (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Dominican Republic (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Ecuador - Bibliography (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Fine Arts (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Indigenismo (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Novela hispanoamericana (cont...) (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Novela hispanoamericana (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Latin america novel (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Novel (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - El Salvador (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Graduate students, theses, proposals and abstracts (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Subseries P: Student papers on mexican literature and culture, and various topics. A-Z
    - Azuela, Mariano (cont...) (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Azuela, Mariano (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Acuña, Manuel (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Agustín, José (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Altamirano, Ignacio (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Banda Farfán, Raquel (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Campobello, Nellie (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Carpentier, Alejo Arreola, Juan José (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Castellanos, Rosario (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Caso, Alfonso (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Caso, Antonio (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Cravioto, Alfonso (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Cruz, Artemio (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Cuevas, José Luis (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Delgado, Rafael (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Díaz Castillo, Bernal (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Díaz Dufoo, Carlos (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Dolujanoff, Emma (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Fernández, José Joaquín (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Fernández, Justino (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Fernández de Lizardi, José Joaquín (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Frías, Heriberto (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Fuentes, Carlos (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Galindo, Sergio (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Gamboa, Federico (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - García Ponce, Juan (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - González Martínez, Enrique (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Gutiérrez Nájera, Manuel (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Guzmán, Martín Luis (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Henriquez Ureña, Pedro (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Icaza, Francisco A. de (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Kahler, Erich (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Leñero, Vicente (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - López y Fuentes, Gregorio (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - López Portillo y Rojas, José (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - López Velarde, Ramón (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Magdaleno, Mauricio (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - Martínez Sotomayor, José (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Monterde, Francisco (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Monterroso, Augusto (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Muñoz, Rafael F. (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Nájares, Daniel (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Nervo, Amado (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Novo, Salvador (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Pacheco, José Emilio (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Paz, Octavio (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Pellicer, Carlos (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Rabasa, Emilio (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Ramos, Samuel (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Revueltas, José (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Reyes, Alfonso (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Rivera, Diego (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Riva Palacio, Vicente (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Rodríguez Galván, Ignacio (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Rojas González, Francisco (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Romero, José Rubén (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Rosas de Oquendo, Mateo (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Rubín, Ramón (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Rulfo, Juan (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Sabines, Jaime (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Sahagún, Fr. Bernardino de (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - Sainz, Gustavo (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - Salazar Mallén, Rúben (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - Saldívar, G. (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - Santos-Ortiz, Aurelio de los (Box 157, Folder 24)
    - Sierra, Justo (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Silva y Aceves, Mariano (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Torri, Julio (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Traven, B. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Usigli, Rodolfo (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Vasconcelos, José (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Verissimo, Erico (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Villaurrutia, Xavier (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Yañez, Agustín (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Zea, Leopoldo (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Zepeda, Eraclio (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Catholicism and nationalism in Mexico (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - El Huipil, una vestidura tradicional (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Los indumentarios de los antiguos mexicanos (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - The mexican oil expropriation (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - La mujer Zapoteca: Del itsmo de Tehuantepec (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - El papel de los campesinos en la revolución mexicana (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - La política nacional en México (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - La revolución de México: De Madero a Cárdenas (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Taxco (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - El uso del monólogo interior en cuanto a cuatro escritores contemporáneos de México (Box 158, Folder 21)
    - La Virgen de Guadalupe (Box 158, Folder 22)
    - Emiliano Zapata (Box 158, Folder 23)
    - Zinacatan (Box 158, Folder 24)
- Series 7: Reprint information
  - Subseries A: Reprints: (sobretiros), and additional reprints
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. A (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. B (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. C (cont...) (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. C (cont...) (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. C (cont...) (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. C (cont...) (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. C (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. D (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. E (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. F (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. G (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. H (cont...) (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. H (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. J (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. K (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. L (cont...) (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. L (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. M (cont...) (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. M (cont...) (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. M (cont...) (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. M (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. N (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. O (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. P (cont...) (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. P (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. R (cont...) (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. R (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. S (cont...) (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. S (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. T (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets all dedicated to Luis Leal and signed by author. U-Z (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Separatas dedicated to Luis Leal, but not signed by authors (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Separatas given to Luis Leal with a solution and signed by authors. Not actually dedicated to Luis Leal by name. A-Mead (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Separatas given to Luis Leal with a solution and signed by authors. Not actually dedicated to Luis Leal by name. Mejia Sanchez-Vela (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). A (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). B (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). C (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). D (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). E (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). F (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). G (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). H (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). K (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). L (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). M (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). N (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). O-P (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). R (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). S (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). T-U (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). V-W (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). V-W (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Additional miscellaneous reprints (sobretiros). 1. Mexico The amigo country: Mexico's cultural mosaics, foestas, and reports await you. 2. Revista Interamericana de Bibliografía. Indice de contenido y contribuyentes. (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous cards files reprints (Box 165)
  - Subseries B: EL NACIONAL (México): Miscellaneous news papers tearsheets, 1958-1972
    - Jul. 1958-Dec. 1958 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 1959-June 1959 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Jul. 1959-Dec. 1959 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Jan. 1960-June 1960 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Jul. 1960-Dec. 1960 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 1961-June 1961 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Jul. 1961-Dec. 1961 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Jan. 1962-June 1962 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Jul. 1962-Dec. 1962 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 1963-June 1963 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Jul. 1963-Dec. 1963 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Jan. 1964-June 1964 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Jul. 1964-Dec. 1964 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 1965-June 1965 (Box 169, Folder 2)